[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WELL, HERE'S THE
EXCITING CONCLUSION OF MY VISIT
WITH TAYLOR SWIFT AT THE STAPLES
CENTER.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
I AM --
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HI.
I AM TERRIBLY SORRY.
I WAS LOOKING FOR THE LADIES
ROOM.
I AM SO SORRY.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU WANT TO -- DO YOU HAVE AN
INSTRUMENT OR SOMETHING YOU
COULD PLAY, BECAUSE YOU'RE HERE,
YOU KNOW.
YOU HAVE AN INSTRUMENT?
I'LL JUST CHOOSE.
I'LL GO AND GET THAT.
HERE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&l&l
&l I WAS RIDING SHOTGUN WITH MY
HAIR UNDONE IN THE FRONT SEAT OF
HIS CAR &l
&l I GRABBED A PEN AND AN OLD
NAPKIN AND I WROTE DOWN OUR
SONG &l
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ELLEN!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I LOVE YOU, TAYLOR.